"迷失" 前情提要...
Previously on "Lost"...
Juliet啊
Juliet.
都是你干的好事
You did this.
Kate? Hurley啊!
Kate? Hurley!
把他抬起来 送到泉水那边去
Pick him up. Get him to the spring.
水有些浑浊 怎么回事?
The water isn't clear. What happened?
你在帮倒忙! 快淹死他了!
You're not saving him! You're drowning him!
- 你朋友死了  - Jack!
- Your friend is dead.  - Jack!
发生什么事了?
What happened?
他活过来了
He's alive.
生效了?
It worked?
兄弟 你没事啦!
Dude, you're okay!
Hurley 让他喘口气
Hurley, let him breathe.
Miles 你能弄点水来么?
Miles, can you go get some water?
好 我这就去
Yeah, on it.
Sayid 嘿
Sayid. Hey.
你感觉如何?
How are you feeling?
有点头晕
A little light-headed.
Jack啊...
Jack...
我怎么了?
What happened to me?
你死而复生了
You died.
这怎么可能?
How is that even possible?
我是说...
I mean...
他前一会儿才断气 现在又安然无恙?
One minute he's gone, and now he's fine?
他当然没事
Of course he's fine.
什么意思?
What does that mean?
他是个枪杀孩子的伊拉克游客
He's an Iraqi tourer who shoots kids.
没这么容易死
He's definitely deserves another go-around.
你在看什么?
What are you looking at?
你觉得外面有多少持枪分子?
How many guys with guns you think are outside this place?
- 什么?  - 他们带我来的时候 我正处于昏迷中
- What?  - I was out cold when they brought me in here.
你看见多少警卫? 5个? 10个? 100个?
How many guards did you see? Five? Ten? A hundred?
你想做什么?
What are you thinking?
我在计划逃跑 Kate
I'm thinking about running, Kate.
她戴着手铐
She's got hands in handcuffs,
但她可能会把手铐遮起来 明白吗?
but she's probably got 'em covered, okay?
嘿!
Hey!
嘿 看路啊
Hey, watch it.
开车!
Go!
- 快开车!  - 小姐 我已经载客了
- Go now!  - Lady, I already have a customer.
- 混蛋 我叫你开车!  - 好的
- Damn it, I said go!  - Okay.
哦! 慢点 慢点 别开那么快
Ooh! Easy, easy. Slow down.
- 嘿 别开那么快! 慢点!  - 知道! 知道! 你叫我开车的!
- Hey, just slow down. Slow down!  - Okay! Okay! You said go!
把我们带出这里就好
Just get us out of here.
嘿! 嘿! 停车!
Hey! Hey! Stop the cab!
拜托 拜托让我下... 啊!
Please, please just let me out of... Aah!
闭嘴!
Be quiet!
- 你在做什么? 快开车!  - 有人在那儿 我会撞上他的
- What are you doing? Move!  - There's a guy. I'm not gonna run him over.
嘿 我在这里走着呢! 我在走着呢!
Hey. I'm walkin' here! I'm walkin' here!
不要下车
Do not get out of this car.
开车
Just go.
快开车! 别管那家伙! 开车!
Go now! I don't care about the guy! Go!
嘿! 嘿! 你要死啊?!
Hey! Hey! What the hell?!
嘿 我记住你的车牌号了!
Hey, I got your license plate!
前方红绿灯处 左转
At the light, take a left.
拜托... 拜托让我下车 好吗?
Can you... can you please, please just let me go?
- 我保证不会向别人多嘴的  - 嘿!
- I promise I won't say anything to anyone.  - Hey!
嘿!
Hey!
该死的!
Damn it!
拜托 拜托
Please. Please.
把你的钱包给我
Give me your purse.
- 什么?  - 我说 把你的钱包给我!
- What?  - I said, give me your purse!
现在 下车
Now get out of the car.
我能不能... 拿一下行李?
Can I please just... just get my suitcase?
不行! 下车!
No, you can't! Get out of the car!
放轻松
Easy.
这些人是谁?
Who are these people?
他们要干嘛?
What do they want?
是The Others 兄弟
It's The Others, dude.
他们又一次...
They caught us...
抓到了我们
again.
我不清楚 我想 他们在试图保护我们
I don't know. I think they're trying to protect us.
嗯 就... 像你看到的 呃
Yeah, and as... as you can see, uh,
Hugo在这里 被当做头儿看待
Hugo here has assumed the leadership position,
可以说... 这样很棒
So... that's pretty great.
怎么了?
What?
你的伤口
The wound.
几乎完全愈合了
It's almost completely closed.
谢谢你 Jack
Thank you, Jack.
- 谢我什么?  - 谢你救了我的命
- For what?  - Saving my life.
Jarrah先生 请跟我们来下 好吗?
Mr. Jarrah, will you come with us, please?
- 跟你去哪儿?  - 里面 没什么好担心的 我们...
- Come with you where?  - Inside. Nothing to worry about. We...
我跟他一起去
I'm coming with him.
哦 抱歉 我们要跟他单独谈
Oh, I'm sorry. We need to talk to him alone.
- 就几个问题  - 你有几个问题? 正好 我们也是
- Just a few questions.  - You have a few questions? Well, so do we.
我想先问 你们是什么人?
I mean, let's start with, who are you?
你们干嘛把我们囚在这? 你们...
Why are you holding us here? You...
一旦跟Jarrah先生谈过 我们将很乐意告诉你们
Once we've spoken to Mr. Jarrah, we'll be more than happy
你们想知道的一切
to tell you everything you want to know.
我有种预感
Something tells me
你们不会乐意告诉我们任何事
that you're not gonna be happy to tell us anything.
别开枪! 放下武器!
Don't shoot! Lower your weapons!
拜托 你没必要这样做
Please, you don't have to do this.
- 我们不会伤害你的朋友的  - 他不是我朋友
- We won't hurt your friend.  - He ain't my friend.
你高兴把他们怎么样 就怎么样
You do what you want with him and anybody else.
可我? 我要离开这儿
But me? I'm walking outta here.
James啊?
James?
我要离开这里 明白吗?
I'm gone. You understand?
拜托
Please.
你得留下来
You have to stay.
不 我不要
No, I don't.
别跟着我
Don't come after me.
嘿! 嘿!
Hey! Hey!
他们要把Sayid带到哪儿去?
Where are they taking Sayid?
嘿 别激动! 大家都冷静下来!
Hey, calm down! Everybody calm down!
- Ford会去哪儿?  - 什么?
- Where'd Ford go?  - What?
- Ford 你朋友 刚跑出去的那个... 他去哪儿了?  - 我不知道
- Ford. Your friend who just ran out here... Where did he go?  - I don't know.
你真以为我会相信?
You really expect me to believe that?
他说他要杀了我 你信吗?
He told me he wanted to kill me. You believe that?
- 我能把他带回来  - 你知道他去哪儿了?
- I can bring him back.  - You know where he went?
不知道 但我可以追踪到他
No, but I can track him.
让我去吧
Let me go.
我能把他带回来 还能让他留下来
I will bring him back, and I can make him stay.
Kate啊...
Kate...
你确定要单独跟这些人一起去?
You sure you wanna go out there alone with these people?
我跟她一起去
I'll go with her.
他得安全地回来 这很重要
It's very important that he gets back here safely.
你凭什么就认为他会听你的?
What makes you think he's gonna listen to you?
我有把握说服他
I can very convincing when I wanna be.
轮胎锤在哪儿?
Where's your tire hammer?
- 你遇到麻烦了  - 你也是
- You got problem.  - So do you.
轮胎锤在哪儿?
Where's your tire hammer?
轮胎锤会敲断你的手腕
Tire hammer'll just cut off your wrists.
你的麻烦就是 你需要一个冲压机
Your problem is you need a punch press,
可你不可能
and you're not gonna be able
一边用冲压机 一边还用枪指着我
to use one of those and keep that gun pointed at me.
- 你是在主动请缨?  - 我手很稳
- You volunteering?  - I got steady hands,
不过我觉得 我们打见面起就有误会
but I kinda feel like we got off on the wrong foot.
我给你200美元
I'll give you 200 dollars.
别动
Now hold still.
谢谢
Thanks.
因为什么被铐上的?
So why the bracelets?
我因为谋杀被通缉
I'm wanted for murder.
谋杀?
Murder?
你不会刚好有地方 能让我换衣服吧?
You don't happen have somewhere I could change, do you?
浴室在那边
Bathroom's over there.
得快点哦
Make it quick.
谢谢
Thank you.
你最好别拖我们后腿
You better not slow us down.
你们才最好别拖我后腿
You better not slow me down.
我该跟你一起去 可...
I'd go with you, but...
可... Sawyer会杀了你?
But... Sawyer would kill you?
我负责照顾James 你负责照顾Sayid
I'll take care of James. You take care of Sayid.
一言为定
Deal.
再见
Good-bye.
小心点
Be careful.
你想要干嘛?
What is it you want?
求你了 不管你想干什么...
Please, whatever you're thinking of doing...
那是什么?
What is that?
告诉我 你想干什么
Just tell me what you want.
为什么?!
Why?!
你干嘛这么做?
Why are you doing this?
我什么秘密都没有
I don't have any secrets.
问...
Ask...
啊!
Aah!
抱歉 让你受苦了
I'm sorry we had to put you through that.
- 这是个测试 我们得确认一下  - 测来确认什么?
- It was a test. We had to be sure.  - Test to be sure of what?
别担心
Don't worry.
你通过测试了
You passed.
我刚才骗了他 对吧?
I just lied to him, didn't I?
是的
Yes.
你刚才要去哪?
Where were you going?
什么?
What?
在我跳上出租车之前 你要去哪?
Before I got in the cab, where were you going?
问这干嘛 你也想劫持他们?
Why, so you can hijack them, too?
我等公车
I was waiting for a bus.
我来把你的东西给你
I came to bring you stuff.
放心 我没拿你钱
Relax. I didn't take your money.
啊 呃 好吧 谢谢
Well, uh, gee, thanks.
- 那你刚才要去哪?  - 别操心了
- So where were you goin'?  - Don't worry about it.
好吧
Fine.
Langdon大街
Langdon Street.
在Brentwood
Brentwood.
你在那有亲人?
You got family there?
呃 没有
Uh, no.
就是... 一对夫妻要收养我的孩子
It's the... a couple who's adopting my baby.
他们 呃 他们本该来机场接我
They were, hum, they were meant to meet me at the airport,
但是我猜 可能是日子弄错了什么的
but I guess they got the days mixed up or somethin'.
- 他们不像反悔了的样子  - Brentwood不远 上车
- It's not like they abandoned me.  - Brentwood's not far. Get in.
说真的?
Seriously?
你想不想搭车?
Do you want a ride or not?
你们为什么要我们在庙里待着?
So why do you people want us to stay at the temple?
我们在保护你们
We're protecting you.
- 要防什么?  - 你在这岛上待了一段时间 对吗?
- From what?  - You've been on this island for a while, right?
见没见过一丛黑烟...
Ever see a big pillar of black smoke...
- 会发出"嘀嗒嘀嗒"的声音 好像生气了一样?  - 见过
- makes a "ticka ticka" sound, looks pissed off?  - Yes.
防的就是它
From that.
你知道另外一架飞机的事吗?
Do you know anything about another plane coming in?
- 一架Ajira飞机  - 抱歉 这是新闻发布会吗?
- An Ajira flight.  - I'm sorry. Is this a press conference?
我觉得他说的是那架降落...
I think he means the one that landed...
Justin 闭嘴
Justin. Shut up.
不 不 不 那条路是用来迷惑人的
No, no, no, that's a decoy trail.
他从这儿走了
He went this way.
- 你凭什么这么说?  - 经验
- And you're basing this on what?  - Experience.
Aldo呀
Aldo.
干嘛?
What?
我觉得她说对了
I think she's right.
她当然对
Of course she is.
请您带路 公主
After you, princess.
你想用什么办法把男朋友带回来?
So what's your strategy for bringing you boyfriend back?
希望你有辄 因为他出去的时候 射伤了个人
I hope you got one, because he shot a guy on his way out.
- 他要是这么对我的话 我就把他脑袋打爆  - 喂 看着点儿
- If he tries that on me, I'm gonna blow his head off.  - Whoa. Watch it.
谢谢
Thank you.
看着像Rousseau的陷阱
Looks like one of Rousseau's traps.
那法国女人? 不 她已经死了好几年了
The French woman? No, she's been dead for years.
- 这... 这不可能是她的...  - Justin!
- This... this couldn't be one of her...  - Justin!
闭嘴
Shut up.
他要说什么?
What was he gonna say?
你都不记得我了 是吗?
You don't even remember me, do you?
你认不出我?
You don't recognize me?
哦 可能这个会让你想起来
Well, maybe this will jog your memory.
3年前
Three years ago,
你上演了一出越狱 而且你是用
you staged yourself a little prison break, and you did it
来福枪的枪托 敲晕了旁边的警卫
by knocking the guard out with the butt of you rifle.
那个人就是我
That would be me.
你干什么?
What are you doing?
逃跑
Escaping.
Sayid啊!
Sayid!
还好吗 哥们儿?
You okay, man?
Jack! 他回来了!
Jack! He's back!
Sayid 发生什么事了?
Sayid, what happened?
- 他们对我用刑  - 为什么?
- They tortured me.  - Why?
不知道 他们什么也没问
Don't know. They didn't ask any questions.
让开
Step aside.
嘿 Shephard
Hey, Shephard.
我们正盼着你自己过来
We were hoping you'd come on your own.
你们到底对Sayid做了什么?
What the hell did you do to Sayid?
我们... 什么都没做 你... 你朋友病了
We... we didn't do anything to him. Y... your friend is sick.
他是...
He's...
是的 我... 这真的不能...
Yeah, I... It's not really...
这真的直译不了
It's not really a literal translation.
最接近的说法是...
The closest thing would be...
感染
infected.
感染? 他都没有发烧
Infected? He's not even running a fever.
什么意思...
What...
我说了什么好笑的话吗?
Did I say something funny?
我不这么认为 他一点幽默感都没有
I doubt it. He doesn't really have a sense of humor.
他说 你得把这粒药给你朋友
He says you have to give your friend this pill.
你说真的?
Are you serious?
为什么你不自己给他?
Why don't you give it to him?
因为只有他自己愿意吃 才有效果
Because it won't work unless he takes it willingly,
但是由我们给他 他肯定是不情愿的
and won't take it willingly from us.
呃 你们也许该在对他用刑之前
Well, then maybe you should've asked him to take it
- 让他吃药  - 我们没有对他用刑
- before you tortured him.  - We didn't torture him.
- 我们只是在为他诊断  - 看他是不是真感染了
- We were diagnosing him.  - To see if he was infected.
是的
Yes.
除非我知道成分
I'm not gonna give anything to Sayid
否则我不会拿给Sayid
unless I know what's in it.
告诉我 Shephard...
Tell me, Shephard...
你的朋友...
Your friend...
他是怎么中枪的?
How did he get shot?
他是 呃...
He was, um...
他是为了帮助我
He was helping me.
所以 错在你?
So it was your fault?
是的
Yes.
那还有其他人
And there have been others
为了帮你...
who were hurt or died...
而受伤或牺牲了吗?
helping you?
是的
Yes.
那...
Well...
这是你赎罪的机会
Then this is your chance to redeem yourself.
这是药
It's medicine,
你的朋友需要它
and your friend needs it.
我如果不拿给他 会怎么样?
What happens if I don't give it to him?
感染会扩散
The infection will spread.
所以... 没别的了? 啥也没有?
So... nothing? There wasn't anything?
没有白光? 没有天使唱歌?
No white light? Angels singing?
没有死去的亲友?
No dead relatives?
我记得我被打中了
I remember being shot.
你不是变成僵尸了吧?
You're not a zombie, right?
不 我不是僵尸
No. I am not a zombie.
嘿
Hey.
能让我和Sayid单独待会儿么?
You mind giving me and Sayid a minute?
行 知道么 私下谈话总是让我抓狂
Yeah, see, private talks kinda freak me out
因为他们经常会让我做
cause they usually lead
我不是很理解的事情
to me having to do something I don't quite understand.
我懂你的意思
I'm right there with ya.
好 我们在饭厅 有事叫我们
It's fine. We'll be in the food court if you need us.
他们告诉你 用烙铁烫我的原因了吗?
So did they tell you why they burnt me with a hot poker?
他们说是在为你诊断
They said they were trying to diagnose you.
是的
Right.
他们说这是一种测试
They told me it was some sort of test,
而我已经通过了
which they said I passed.
但很明显 我并没有
Clearly, I didn't.
那是什么
What's that?
他们想让你服下这个
They want you to take it.
据他们说 这是药
It's medicine, according to them.
那你认为呢?
What about according to you?
我不知道
I don't know.
你知道吗 在你...
And you know, before when you...
在你谢我救你一命之前 我...
when you thanked me for saving your life, I...
我其实什么也没做 Sayid
I didn't have anything to do with it, Sayid.
不是我救的你 是他们
I didn't fix you. They did.
我不在乎救我的是谁
I don't care who fixed me.
我在乎的是我信任谁
I only care about who I trust,
所以 如果你说要我吃那粒药 Jack
so if you want me to take that pill, Jack,
我就吃
I'll do it.
等下 你要去哪?
Wait. Where are you going?
赶上Sawyer
Catching up with Sawyer.
你从没想过把他带回庙里
So you never planned to bring him back to the temple.
不 我不想坐牢 你也不想吧?
No. I'm not interested in being a prisoner. Are you?
- Kate 你们飞机在哪降落的?  - 什么?
- Where did your plane land, Kate?  - What?
你和Jack和Hurley坐的那架Ajira飞机...
The Ajira plane that you, Jack and Hurley came in on...
- 在哪降落的?  - 我不知道
- Where did it land?  - I don't know.
Sun也在那架飞机上 我得找到她
Sun was on that plane, too, and I have to find her.
你觉得他们会告诉你吗?
You think they're gonna tell you?
你认为他们会关心你 Sun 或者我们中的谁吗?
You think they care about you or about Sun or about any of us?
那你关心谁 Kate?
Who do you care about, Kate?
祝你好运 Jin
Good luck, Jin.
你找到Sawyer后... 打算怎么办?
Once you catch up with Sawyer... then what?
我想我们会一起商量下一步的行动
I guess we'll figure that out together.
嗯 那么...
So, uh...
你的手铐呢?
What happened to your handcuffs?
我找人砍断了
I cut them off.
这里环境真好
It's a beautiful neighborhood.
他们一定是一对和善的夫妇
I bet they're a really nice couple.
怎么了?
What?
我什么都没说啊
I didn't say anything.
你... 你认为他们是故意没来机场接我的?
What, you... you think they didn't come to the airport on purpose?
我为什么要那么想?
Why would I think that?
那就好 我知道他们不是故意的
Good, because they didn't.
到了
This is it.
嗯...
Um...
你能陪我一起进去吗?
Will you come in with me?
开什么玩笑?
Are you kidding me?
拜托 我... 我只是...
Please, I... I just...
我真的不想独自进去
I really don't want to go up there on my own.
呃 嗨 是Baskum太太吗? 我... 我是Clair Littleton
Uh, hi. Uh, Mrs. Baskum? I'm... I'm Clair Littleton
哦 天哪
Oh, my god.
真抱歉
I'm so so sorry.
呃...
Um...
我丈夫...
My husband...
抛弃了我 相信我
He left me. And believe me,
我的确也非常想要这个孩子
I wanted the baby so much,
但是...
But...
我一个人 真的负担不了
I can't do it alone.
对不起
I'm sorry.
是 我知道 我早该打电话告诉你的
Look, I know I should've called you
所以 呃 那么...
So, uh, what...
你... 你... 你就这样反悔了?
Y... y... you just changed your mind?
瞧 我... 我的生活已经...
Look, my... my life is just...
已经一团糟了
a little bit complicated.
她大老远从澳大利亚跑来 可你却连电话都不打一个?
She came all the way from Australia, and you don't call?
哦 我的天哪
Oh, my god.
你还好吗?
Are you Ok?
啊! 我要生了!
Aah! It's coming!
谁在那儿?
Who's there?
马上出来
Better come out now
否则 我就开枪了
or so help me, I'm just gonna start shooting.
你来这干什么?
What the hell are you doing here?
我很担心你
I was worried about you.
她是怎么了?
What's happening?
- 我... 我想我已经宫缩了  - 什么时候开始的?
- I... I think I'm having contractions.  -  When did they start?
- 呃 大概20分钟前  - 试着放松
- Um, about 20 minutes ago.  - Try to relax.
我们马上带你去检查
We're gonna take you to the M.F.C.U. to get looked at.
你和她一起的?
Are you with her?
- 是  - 好 跟我走
- Yeah.  - Okay, follow me.
你在干什么? 这... 这是怎么了?
What are you doing? What... what's going on?
稍等 医生马上就来
Hold on. The doctor will be with you in just a moment.
- 怎... 怎么样现在?  - 有什么问题吗?
- What... what's going on?  - Is something wrong?
请问
Excuse me.
- 嗨  - 你是医生吗?
- Yes.  - Are you a doctor?
- 是 我是Goodspeed医生  - 能麻烦你过来看看吗?
- Yes. I'm Dr. Goodspeed.  - Can I please get your help in here?
Littleton小姐?
Ms. Littleton?
Claire 你感觉怎么样?
Claire, how are you feeling?
很不舒服 怎... 怎么了我这是?
Uncomfortable, What... w... what's happening?
怎么了...
What's happening...
你的小宝宝已经迫不及待 要叫妈妈了
Is that motherature has gotten a little ahead of herself.
你准备好面对他了吗?
Are you ready to have your baby?
- 我... 不好意思 你说什么?!  - 你已经怀孕36周了
- I... I'm sorry. What?!  - You're at 36 weeks.
扩张了3厘米 80%的羊水也破了
3 centimeters dilated and about 80% effaced.
就是说 只要你愿意 今晚你就可以生了
Which means, if you want, You can have your baby tonight.
如果我愿意? 那么 就是说... 你也可以阻止不生?
If I want? So at, you mean... you mean you can stop it then?
应该可以 但是 那要注射大量麻药
Maybe. However, to do that would require number of drugs.
麻药? 那么... 会伤害到宝宝吗?
Drugs? I mean, w... will that hurt the baby?
不 他们相当安全
No, they are perfectly safe.
我只是不想
I just don't want to have to
无谓地 给你注射药物
stick you with needless if I don't have to.
所以 完全取决于你
So is up to you.
我... 我还没准备好
I'm... I'm not ready.
那好 马上给她静脉注射
OK. Let's get her started on the ifedipine drip.
这... 这... 这是什么意思?
Wh... what... what is it?
Margaret 给她做超声波检测
Margaret, let's do her ultrasound.
我想知道发生什么了
I wanna get a piece of what's going on in there.
这... 可能是婴儿的位置不对了
It... it could just mean the baby's out of position.
你... 你... 你在说什么?!
W... w... what are you... what are you saying?!
我... 我的... 孩子发生什么了?!
W... what... what's happening to my baby?!
我孩子还好吗?!
Is my baby okay?!
Aaron好吗?!
Is Aaron okay?!
看?
See?
他在那儿 一切都好
There he is. Everything is just fine.
你的孩子就是喜欢乱动
Your boy just likes to move around.
是140 b.p.m
140 b.p.m.
非常正常
Perfectly normal.
我有一种感觉
I have a feeling
Aaron会是个很不好管的人
And Aaron is gonna be a handful.
现在让我们看看 是否可以把这个降低
Now let'see if we can slow this down.
你做得好极了 母亲
You did great, mommy.
多谢
Thanks.
几天前
A couple days ago,
你问我为什么回到这个岛上
you asked me why I came back to the island.
我要找到Claire
I need to find Claire.
我本以为...
I thought...
也许如果我能赶上你 你就能帮我
maybe if I could catch up to you, you could help me,
然后...
and then...
也许我们可以找到他 并把他带回Aaron身边
maybe if we could find her and bring her back to Aaron,
那么所有这些 就不会徒然无功了
then maybe all of this wouldn't have been for nothing.
对不起 我不该跟着你
I'm sorry. I never should followed you.
什么时候?
Which time?
那是你的房子 对吧? 和Juliet的
That was your house, right? With Juliet.
是的
Yep.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你已经说过了
You already said that.
不...
No...
对Juliet说的
For Juliet.
如果我没在潜艇上跟着你
If I hadn't come after you on the sub,
你们两个就会离开 她也不会死了
then you two would've left, and she would've never died.
她的死 不是你的错
It's not your fault she's dead.
我的错
It's mine.
她就坐在那儿
She was sittin' right there,
就是你现在坐的地方
right where you are now,
努力离开这个地方
tryin' to leave this place.
我说服她留了下来
And I convinced her to stay.
我让她留在这个岛上
I made her stay on this island
因为我不想一个人
'Cause I didn't want to be alone.
你能理解的 对吧?
You understand that, right?
但是 呃...
But, uh...
但是我觉得 我们有些人
But I think some of us
注定是要孤独的
are meant to be alone.
我本打算 向她求婚的
I was gonna ask her to marry me
你大概可以在日落之前 回到庙里的
You can probably make it back to the temple by nightfall.
那是什么?
What's that?
一个棒球
It's a baseball.
对一个需要翻译的人来说
You speak pretty good English
你英语说得还真不错
for someone that needs a translator.
我们都知道 我不需要翻译
We both know that I don't need a translator.
那为什么你有个翻译
Then why do you have one.
因为我必须
Beause I have to remain separate
和被我管理的人们 分开
from the people I'm in charge of.
事情会简单一些
Makes it easier
即使他们不喜欢 我为他们做的决定
when they don't like the decisions I make for them.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我的名字叫Dogen
My name is Dogen.
你是这儿的... 岛上的人?
Are you from here... The island?
我和其他所有人一样 是被带到这来的
I was brought here like everyone else.
"带到这儿" 是什么意思?
What do you mean, "brought here"?
你很清楚我的意思
You know exactly what I mean.
你没把那药给你朋友 是么?
You didn't give your friend the pill, did you?
没有
No.
为什么?
Why not?
因为我不知道里面是什么
Because I don'know what's in it.
- 它可以消除...  - 感染
- It will eliminate...  - The infection,
是的 我知道
yeah, I got that.
- 但到底是什么?  - 我解释不清
- But what's in it?  - I can't explain.
- 试试看  - 没有时间了
- Try.  - There isn't any time.
- 如果你不给他 他就会死...  - 他已经死了
- He'll die if you don't...  - He already died.
到底是什么?
What is in it?
你只要相信我
You just have to trust me.
我连我自己都不相信
I don't trust myself.
我又该怎么信任你?
How am I supposed To trust you?
让我们看看 信任到底有啥结果
Let's see where trust gets us.
现在 你可以告诉我
Now, are you gonna tell me
里面是什么了吧?
what's in it?
毒药
Poison.
进来
Come in.
打扰一下 Littleton女士
Excuse me. Ms. Littleton
呃 啥事?
Um, yeah?
我是Rasmussen警探
I'm Dtective Rasmussen.
- Hart女士在吗?  - 抱歉 你说谁?
- Is Ms. Hart here?  - Uh, I'm sorry. Who?
Joan Hart 她跟你一起登记的
Joan Hart. She signed in with you.
哦 她是 出租车司机
Oh. She was just the, um, the cab driver.
我需要帮助 是她带我来这儿的
I needed help, and she brought me up here.
他们给我治疗后 她就离开了
She left after they treated me, though.
那她
Did she, uh,
有没有跟你说 她去哪了?
give you any indication where she was headed?
为什么? 出什么事了吗?
Why? Is something wrong?
没事 没啥需要你担心的 走 我们走
No. It's nothing for you to worry about. Come on. Let's go.
谢谢
Thanks.
不客气
Sure.
谢谢
Thank you.
为什么... 他们要追捕你?
Why... why are they after you?
你... 做过什么?
What... what did you do?
如果我说自己是无辜的 你会相信我吗?
Would you believe me if i said I was innocent?
会的 我会
Yeah, I will.
我该走了
Well, I should go.
哦 等等...
Oh, wait. Um...
给 拿上我的信用卡
Here. Take my credit card.
不了
No.
这确实不算什么 但至少能有点用
There's not much of a limit on it, but it's something.
- 你不必这么做  - 你也不必做之前做过的事
- You don't have to do this.  - You didn't have to do what you did either.
Aaron这个名字不错
Aaron's a great name.
我不知道我为何选它 好像是...
I don't know why I said it. It's like...
我不知道 我知道点什么吧
I don't know. I knew it or something.
我认为你该留下他
I think you should keep him.
嗯 祝你好运
Well, um, good luck.
好
Yeah.
你也是
You, too.
谢谢
Thanks.
他吞下去了?
He swallowed it?
是的
Yes.
这是什么?
What's this?
茶
Tea.
你们为什么想杀Sayid?
Why would you people want to kill Sayid?
我们相信他已经被...
We believe he has been...
最贴切的翻译是"被索取"
closest translation is "claimed."
被索取
Claimed.
被什么索取?
By what?
他体内的暗黑势力正在滋长
There is a darkness growing in him.
一旦到达他的心脏
And once it reaches his heart,
你曾经的朋友...
everything your friend once was...
就会消失了
will be gone.
不 我...
No, I...
你怎么确定的?
How can you be sure of that?
因为此事发生在你妹妹身上过
Because it happened to your sister.
起来!
Get up!
这个 补偿我的头
That's for my head.
快说...
Now...
- 那婊子在哪?  - 我不知道
- Where's that bitch?  - I don't know.
- 你不明白 我要回庙里去!  - 嗯 对
- You don't understand. I'm going back to the temple!  - Yeah, right.
看来他是孤身一人 或许我们该带他回去
It looks like he's alone. Maybe we should take him back.
或许 我们找到的 就是个死人
Or maybe we didn't find him alive.
Aldo 不要 我们不能 他是其中之一
Aldo, no. We can't. He's one of them.
他可能是其中之一
He may be one of them.
嘿! 嘿!
Hey! Hey!
啊! 呃!
Aah! Uhh!
你想跑哪?
Where you goin'?
Claire吗?
Claire?